Quan Li

Address: PO BOX 73151, Davis, CA 95617

Phone: (626)560-7811 Email: <u>quali@ucdavis.edu</u> Site: uscn.github.io

Summary

Multi-layered background with unique vision. Proficient knowledge in programming, statistics, and analytics. Excellent understanding of data analysis packages in python and R for effective data analysis. Programmer with 3 years of experience in web application development.

Education

University of California, Davis, CA

Bachelor of Science, Computational Statistics, June 2017

Work Experience

RMA Associate Jun 2012- Jun 2015 Aberdeen LLC, Santa Fe Spring, CA

- Disposition of RMAs.
- Communication with Sales and Customer service team on status of RMAs.
- Summary reporting analysis on a weekly and month to month basis including RMA Status and Trend charts.
- Created a web application for checking the inventory and conditions of returned server chassis

Wood Floor Installer Jan 2011- May 2012 Decoration Company, Las Angeles, CA

• Install wood floor

Java Web Application Developer Sep 2007- Sep 2010 Tianyuan Technology Co. Ltd, Shenyang, China

- Performed web applications design and development for clients
- Maintained and supported clients' applications and interfaces
- Created a program to sync database between server
- Used struts spring hibernate architecture

Skills

- Expert in Python, R, and SQL
- Programming (HTML, CSS, Java, JQuery, Ajax)
- Data analysis and modeling

Languages

English and Chinese